KATELYN MICHALOVE

Senior UX Designer

katelynmichalove@gmail.com katelynmichalove.com

615-613-5617

EXPERIENCE

Sunbelt Rentals

Senior UX Designer / May 2021 - Present
UX Designer / Aug 2020 - May 2021
Junior UX Designer / July 2019 - Aug 2020

Sunbeltrentals.com

Design lead for the complete redesign of Sunbelt Rentals' primary digital touch point. As a part of this effort, I conducted stakeholder interviews, user interviews, launched a customer survey, and took designs from wireframes to launch. As a result, we saw a 50% decrease in time to task and a 50% increase in online payments.

• Dispatch and Logistics Platform

Product redesign to identify inefficiencies and increase transportation profitability. This involved field interviews and observations, wireframing new solutions and features to solve dispatcher needs, utilizing and contributing to a design system, usability testing and iteration.

• SmartEquip - iOS Mobile Inspection Application

1 Week sprint redesign to improve the user flows, match iOS HIG, and convert visual design to Sunbelt Rentals branding guidelines. Solved usability issues discovered in field pilot testing.

Freelance / Product Designer

August 2018- July 2019

• Baseball analytics website to help launch a new business.

Procter and Gamble / Process Engineer

June 2017 - July 2018

 Led troubleshooting for the chemical plant to solve for process improvement areas.

EDUCATION

University of Tennessee / 2017 / BA Chemical EngineeringBloc / 2019 / UX Design Apprenticeship

SUMMARY

I am a Senior UX Designer with skills in conducting user research and leading projects from wireframe to launch. I am datadriven and seek out analytics, user research, and competitive insight to drive design decision. I collaborate with the team to define requirements and develop a product that solves users' problems while meeting business objectives.

TOOLS

Sketch, Figma

Marvel, Invision

Adobe Creative Suite

Dovetail

Lookback

Miro, Figjam

Survey Gizmo/Alchemer

Git, GitHub

Google Analytics

HTML, CSS

Jira, Confluence

SKILL SET

User Experience Design

User Research

Market Research

Usability Testing

Information Architecture

Visual Design

Branding

Prototyping

Frontend Development